today we are going to play NomiFactory
after claiming our welcome tablet
we quickly use its scanner app to find some diamonds
which we can collect with our gifted hammer
and to celebrate our wealth
we have also been given some cake
apparently eating with dirty hands gave us hallucinations
so we started building a platform of stone to avoid falling in our dreams
on this new foundation, we shall start laying down the first furnaces and chests to store all of the materials we just mined
with that stuff we make our first steam machinery
required to craft a Bricked Blast Furnace to get access to steel
and acquiring steel means that we can now build LV machinery
which we use to build an Electric Blast Furnace
which, as usual, we shall power with solar boilers
and with that, we are now in the MV age
to progress further, we will need some polyethylene
which was also the only thing we needed to unlock AE2
and that will be of great help inside our new clean room to craft the complex new circuits
and the first usage for our new circuitry is a Vacuum Freezer
which will allow us to harden titanium
and with that we can now craft a drill capable of mining the whole height of a vein in a single click
that way, we can easily gather the materials required to expand our solar boiler generator setup
but those Large Steam Turbines didn't last longer than their rotors
because we already have a Large Combustion Engine
however, we can't run it because we don't have an appropriate dynamo hatch
and making one is a whole new rabbit hole
which starts from making rocket fuel to send a micro miner in a pocket microverse
however, after purifying the tungsten and mixing it with steel
we figure out we have to upgrade our EBF to RTM coils in order to melt it
and to get those we only lack of ruthenium
so we quickly improvise the first half of a platline
with that we can now get the RTM coils
thus smelt the tungsten steel for a dynamo for our combustion generator
to power it, we only use the best fuel, high octane gasoline
and that made our old solar boiler setup obsolete
since it's in the way, we shall do some cleanup
and we can use all of that space we just made for our new PBI production plant
next we make some more multiblocks to expand our workshop
however, it turns out that some recipes can't be done in the wild like that
so we built a proper environment around the delicate machines
now the issue was that the light bulbs kept popping
to get enough material for all of those and the future upgrades
we made a huge ore processing and sorting facility
then to keep up with the new energy consumption
we changed the color of the Combustion Generators
but our old cables couldn't keep up with that much power
so we made a power substation to properly split it across all of our base
now we have powerful machines for everything
but those aren't better than the single block version yet
to make them stand out, we need Parallel Control Hatches
however, crafting those will require a lot of nether stars
and since we are playing in hard mode
we are locked in peaceful difficulty
that means no wither farms
so the best way to obtain these is to get them from another universe
thus, we equip our tier 4 Microverse Mining Drone with some swords to do the task
making it tier four and a half
once built, we send it in our slightly bigger version of microverse
and we wait for the loot to come back
finally, we use all of those rods to craft a nether star
moving on, the next full tier rocket is the tier 5
but this one will need better fuel
such as plutonium
after quickly diving deep into nuclear craft
we managed to salvage some
which we use to power our new rocket
and get some minerals from which we can extract naquadah
with that, we can make coils capable of melting trinium
which makes even better coils
and it doesn't stop there
with trinium we can also make superconducting coils
those aren't for a blast furnace
but for something that will be built by our new Assembly Line
a Fusion Reactor
this is a huge toroidal structure that
after charging up with a lot of energy
will start fusing light elements to create new ones that can't be found in nature
such as europium
and with that new material we can start crystallizing some chips
that can be used to go beyond the limitations of silicon
making a new series of more advanced processors
however, single steps of those circuits and their components are starting to take way more energy than our combustion generator could produce
to fix that issue
we added some powerful solar panels
but those didn't keep up for long
one of the main issues is that they don't always work
and as the sun sets
we take a deep breath
then we exhale our blazing pyrotheum and high octane gasoline dragon breath on some metal dust to make it draconic
we give that dust a quick heating in our blast furnace with the addition of some gasoline
and cool it down into an ingot
we make this material pass multiple times inside our new Fusion Crafter
until we manage to craft a new tier of rocket out of it
and this one requires a new tier of Microverse Projector
this time we will be scouting for dragon hearts
which we shall use to make a Celestial Manipulator to make the nights fly away
and the way this machine actually works
is by distracting us with cool animations for long enough for the sun to rise naturally
anyways, after all of that
we can go back to our research for new materials
and what we found out is that
with a new tier of Fusion Reactor
we can get tritanium
and the first thing we can do with it is to upgrade our Clean Room into a Sterile Room
however, since that upgrade was expensive
we made a smaller one on the side
and we made sure to optimize the space we have inside it
with this new sterile environment
we can now make stem cells
as usual, making progress will make the sheep poor
sorry, fat cows medditors
but we shall ignore it
and move on to our old clean room
where we can make the best circuit boards available
then we build some neuroprocessing boards on those for our new wetware circuits
however, we are not yet capable of clustering those into a mainframe
that is because we do not have enough computation power for that research
so we upgrade our computer
but that was still not enough
so we built a Network Switch to chain even more computers together
thus reaching the needed computation for our new circuit
this data orb is bigger than the previous ones
so it has to be read by a data bank to be used
and with that, we now have unlocked the highest tier of circuit in the game
which we shall use to make the highest tier of Fusion Reactor
which will allow us to produce the material required for the highest tier of Micro Universe Harvester
but it's not enough on its own
and of all of the materials required
the one we miss is omnium
which is an amalgamate of every early game material
so, after collecting a stack of each one of those materials
we managed to finally build the highest tier of rocket
which produced the half of an universe
the first use we have for those is Stabilizing Micro Miners
this will make them strong enough to come back from their missions
thus giving us virtually infinite goodies
all at the cost of building one extra multiblock with the cost of about half a Fusion Reactor
and with that, we can go back on our road to the infinity ingot
and you might notice there is no infinite tank here
so instead of the iconic fluid solidifier spam
we shall have extractor spam
but we are also going to need more air collectors
so we get a PA
then we upgrade and even cluster it
and all of this air must be cooled with our new chiller
and distilled with a bigger Fractionating Tower
next we shall also build a couple more fusion reactors
but fluids are not the only issue
we shall also have a bigger blast furnace
which we can build with the help of the new app of our tablet
this rotary half furnace is going to melt 4 stacks of items at once
using UIV power
and all of those items are then processed in our new Assembly Line cluster
to power all of those new machines
we needed something special
we tried various methods
but the best solution was the most simple one
using a tick accelerator on Neutronium Solar Panels
the bottleneck is the energy converters
and we are already using the best kind
also, this setup makes way more energy than our decorative disco balls combined
and now that we fixed about all of the main issues
we can start working on the Creative Chest
to get one we will need a lot of materials
most of them are passively produced
so we can just wait a little bit
there are also some items for which we haven't prepared a recipe yet
but one thing caught our attention, apples
we can get those either by opening loot boxes or with social engineering
but rather than doing those two things
I'd say we can touch some grass
and collect apples like Newton did
by letting them hit us on our head
thus gaining the insight and inspiration to build a machine that does this task for us
with that out of the way
we can start crafting the parts of our objective one at a time
while trying to fix the bottlenecks
so we build more fusion reactors
faster solidifiers
accelerated ultimate crafting
a second Draconic Crafter
more Microverse Projectors
more actuators
more Alloy Blast Smelters
more Fusion Reactors
a bigger Royal Distillery Plant
a bigger Breeder Reactor
a thing that simplifies annoying craftings
however, to power all of those machines
we needed a more versatile energy source
so we quickly craft an Infinite GT EU Emitter
which we set to really high settings
and then attach a peer to peer to
now we can start throwing 16 amps UHV energy hatches everywhere
or at least wherever we can
otherwise, like with fusion reactors
we will simply be building more of it
and now we go back to fixing bottlenecks
such as our soul binder
we make more subnetted mixers
add some more LCR clusters
increase our cobblestone production and storage capacity
stare at our cobblestone stocks
we add a bunch more crafting units
increase our Mega Blast Furnace count
we overclock our Nuclear Reactor
we increase our packaging capacity
we build more electrolyzers
we add more Fusion Reactors
we overhaul the plastic production
we increase our air collection
we have many more packages
and build more and more overclock package crafters
we build more Fusion Reactors
we increase our sugarcane farming capability
we accelerated a full scale nuke craft reactor
and after completing the third Fusion Tower
we can start assembling the most expensive item of the pack
the Creative Chest
and since we have no time
to waste to craft it quicker
we are going to use the power sources of our base
and now that we put together all the pieces
the Creative Chest is finally ours
and with it in our hands
we can finally say that we completed this modpack
and we can move on to the next one
bye bye
今天我们要玩 NomiFactory
在领取新手平板礼包之后
我们很快用它的扫描功能找到了几颗钻石
可以用赠送的锤子收集它们
为了庆祝这泼天富贵
我们得到了些蛋糕
显然，用脏手吃东西会让人产生幻觉
所以我们搭了块石头平台，免得在梦里跌落
在这个新平台上，我们放下熔炉和存放刚开采的材料的箱子
用这些材料我们造出了第一批蒸汽机械
来造出砖高炉，用来炼钢
有了钢，我们现在可以制造 LV 的机器了
用来造电高炉
一如既往，我们用太阳能锅炉给它供能
就这样，我们进入了 MV 时代
要继续发展，我们需要一些聚乙烯
这也是解锁 AE2 的唯一前置条件
这对我们在新洁净间里制作复杂电路帮助很大
新电路的第一个用途是制造真空冷冻机
它能让我们硬化钛
有了它，我们能做出一次点击就能挖完整条矿脉的电钻
这样我们就能轻松收集扩建太阳能锅炉所需的材料
但那些大型蒸汽涡轮的寿命甚至不如转子
因为我们有了一台大型内燃机
不过我们无法运行它——我们缺少合适的动力仓
制作它又是另一个大坑
从制造火箭燃料、把微型矿机送入袖珍微宇宙开始
但在提纯钨并与钢混合后
我们发现必须把 EBF 升级为 RTM 线圈才能熔化它
而要获得这些线圈，我们只差钌
于是我们快速做了铂处理的前半段
有了它我们就能拿到 RTM 线圈
从而熔炼出用于内燃发电机的动力仓的钨钢
我们只打算用最好的燃料“高辛烷值汽油”给它供能
这让旧的太阳能锅炉装置变得多余
既然碍事，我们就清理掉它
把腾出的空间用来建新的 PBI 工厂
接着我们做更多多方块机器来扩展车间
不过有些配方不能露天完成
因此我们为精密机器搭建了合适的环境
当时的问题是灯泡老是爆
为了给这些灯泡和未来的升级获取足够的材料
我们建了个大型矿石加工与分拣设施
接着，为应对新增的电力需求
我们更换了内燃发电机的颜色
但旧电缆承载不了那么多电力
所以我们建了个变电站，把电力合理分配到基地各处
现在我们有了各种强力机器
但它们还未必比单方块版本更强
要让它们变强，我们需要并行控制仓
然而制作这些需要大量下界之星
而我们是在硬核模式下游玩
被锁在和平难度里
这意味着不能建凋灵农场
所以最好的办法就是从另一个宇宙取得它们
于是我们给四阶微宇宙采矿无人机配了把剑去完成任务
把它变成了四阶半
做好后把它送进稍大一点的微宇宙
然后等着战利品回来
最后我们用那些棒子合成了一颗下界之星
接下来的完整阶火箭是 5 阶
但那需要更好的燃料
比如钚
在快速深入核制造之后
我们设法回收到一些材料
用来为新火箭供能
并获取了可以提取出硅岩的矿物
有了它我们能制造出能熔化三元金属的线圈
从而做出更高阶的线圈
而且这还没完
我们还能用三元金属制造超导线圈
这些不是给高炉用的
而是给我们新装配线将要做的东西准备的
也就是聚变堆
它是一个巨大的环形结构
在注入大量能量后
会开始将轻元素聚变成自然界中不存在的新元素
比如铕
凭借这种新材料我们可以开始制作晶体芯片
用于突破硅基的限制
打造一系列更先进的处理器
但那类电路及其组件的单步能耗已经远超我们的内燃发电机
为了解决这个问题
我们增加了一些高功率太阳能板
但它们很快就跟不上了
主要问题之一是它们并不总是可用
当太阳落下时
我们深吸一口气
然后对一些金属粉呼出烈焰之炽焱与高辛烷值汽油的“龙息”，让它变成龙级材料
在高炉里快速加热该粉末并加入少量汽油
再冷却成锭
我们让这种材料在新的龙研聚合装置中多次加工
直到用它制造出五阶的火箭
这次需要更高阶的微宇宙投影仪
这次我们要去搜寻龙心
用它做天体操纵器，把夜晚赶走
这台机器的实际做法是
用炫酷的动画把我们一直吸引住，等太阳自然升起
不管怎样，完成这些之后
我们可以回去继续研究新材料
我们发现
有了新一阶的聚变堆
我们可以获得三钛
我们用它做的第一件事是把洁净间升级为无菌室
然而，由于那项升级成本很高
我们在旁边建了一个小一点的版本
并对内部空间进行了优化
有了这个新的无菌环境
我们现在可以制造干细胞了
像往常一样，进步会让羊变穷
抱歉，是肥牛调解员
但我们会忽略它
接着回到我们原来的洁净间
在那里我们可以制造出最好的电路板
然后我们在其上制作神经元处理器基板，用于新的湿件电路
然而，我们还不能将它们集成成主机
那是因为我们的研究算力还不够
所以我们升级了计算机
但这仍然不够
于是我们搭建了一个网络交换机，将更多计算机串联起来
从而为我们的新电路板提供所需的算力
这个数据球比之前的大得多
因此必须由数据库来读取才能使用
有了它我们就解锁了游戏中最高阶的电路板
我们将用它来制造最高阶的聚变堆
这将使我们能够生产最高阶微宇宙采矿机所需的材料
但单靠它还不够
在所有所需材料中
我们缺少的就是 Omnium
它是所有早期游戏材料的混合物
因此，在收集了每种材料的一整堆之后
我们终于成功建造了最高阶的火箭
它产出了一半的宇宙
我们最先用它来稳定微型矿机
这能让它们强到能从任务中带着战利品回来
从而给我们几乎无限的资源
所有这些以建设一个额外多方块为代价，成本大约相当于半座聚变堆
有了这些，我们就能回到通往无限锭的道路上
你可能会注意到这里没有无限水槽
因此我们不会用标志性的流体固化器去刷屏
而是采用提取器刷屏
但我们还需要更多的空气收集器
所以我们弄了一个 PA
然后对它进行升级，甚至集群化
所有这些空气都要通过我们的新冷却器冷却
并用更大的分馏塔进行蒸馏
接下来我们还会建造几座聚变堆
但液体并不是唯一的问题
我们还要一座更大的高炉
我们可以借助平板电脑的新应用来建造它
这个旋转半炉一次会熔化整整四堆物品
使用 UIV 电力
然后这些物品会在我们的新装配线集群中被加工处理
为所有这些新机器提供动力
为此我们需要一些特殊手段
我们尝试了各种方法
但最好的解决办法往往是最简单的
在中子太阳能电池板上使用滴答加速器
真正的瓶颈是能量转换器
而我们已经在使用最好的那种了
而且，这套系统产生的能量远超过我们那些装饰性迪斯科球的总和
现在我们已经解决了大部分主要问题
可以开始着手制作创意箱了
要做出一个创意箱，我们需要大量材料
而其中大多数是被动产出的
所以我们可以稍微等一段时间
还有一些物品的配方我们尚未准备好
但有一件事引起了我们的注意：苹果
我们可以通过开战利品箱或进行社交工程来获取它们
但我们并不打算采用这两种方法
我想我们可以去“碰点草”（touch some grass）
像牛顿那样收集苹果
让它们砸到我们的头上
从而获得灵感，去造一台替我们完成这项任务的机器
有了它之后
我们就可以开始逐一制作目标所需的部件
同时修复那些瓶颈
所以我们建造了更多聚变堆
更快的固化器
加速终极合成
第二台龙级制造器
更多微宇宙投影仪
更多执行器
更多合金高炉
更多聚变堆
更大的皇家酿酒厂
更大的增殖反应堆
一个用来简化繁琐合成的装置
然而，为了驱动所有这些机器
我们需要更通用的能源来源
于是我们快速制作了一个无限 GT EU 发射器
并把它调到非常高的设置
然后接上点对点（peer-to-peer）连接
现在我们可以到处放置 16 安培的 UHV 能量舱口
至少把它们放到可用位置
否则，就像对待聚变堆那样
我们就干脆再建更多
现在我们又回去修复瓶颈了
比如我们的灵魂绑定器
我们制造了更多子网混合器
并新增了更多 LCR 集群
扩展鹅卵石的生产与存储能力
监控我们的鹅卵石库存
我们增加了更多工艺单元
增加巨型高炉数量
我们对核反应堆进行了超频
我们提高了打包产能
我们制造了更多电解槽
我们建造了更多聚变堆
我们大幅改造了塑料生产线
我们提高了空气收集量
我们还有很多物资包要处理。
并建立了越来越多的超频包装设施
我们又建造了更多聚变堆
我们提高了甘蔗种植产能
（燃尽了）
我们对一座全尺寸核反应堆进行了超频
在完成第三座聚变塔之后
我们就能开始组装包里最昂贵的物品了
创意箱
由于时间有限
我们要迅速完成它
我们要利用基地的能量资源
现在我们把所有部件拼装在一起
创意箱终于属于我们了
它已经到我们手中
我们终于可以说，我们完成了这个模组包
我们可以开始下一个了
再见